const unit6Problems = [{
    //--------------------------------------------SECTION 6.1 ----------------------------------
        //25
        id: 127,
        question: "Sketch the region whose area is given by the definite integral $ \\int_{0}^{\\>4} \\>\\it x \\,dx$. Then use a geometric formula to evaluate the integral.",
        answer: "8",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.1",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //27
        id: 128,
        question: "Sketch the region whose area is given by the definite integral $ \\int_{0}^{\\>2} \\>3{\\it x} + 4 \\>\\it dx$. Then use a geometric formula to evaluate the integral.",
        answer: "14",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.1",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //37
        id: 129,
        question: "Given that $ \\int_{2}^{\\>6} \\>{\\it x} \\>{\\it dx} = 16$, evaluate $ \\int_{2}^{\\>6} \\>({\\it x}-14) \\>\\it dx$.",
        answer: "-40",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.1",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //49c
        id: 130,
        question: "Given that $ \\int_{0}^{\\>5} \\>{\\it f(x)} \\>{\\it dx} = 4$, evaluate $ \\int_{-5}^{\\>5} \\>{\\it f(x)} \\>\\it dx, \\> {\\it f}$ is even.",
        answer: "8",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.1",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //51
        id: 131,
        question: "Evaluate $ \\int_{0}^{\\>8} \\>{\\it f(x)} \\>\\it dx$ for ${\\it f(x)} = { \\begin{Bmatrix} 4, & {\\it x} < 4 \\\\ {\\it x}, & {\\it x} \\geq 4 \\end{Bmatrix}}$.",
        answer: "40",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.1",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    },
    //--------------------------------------------SECTION 6.2 ----------------------------------
    {
        //29
        id: 132,
        question: "Find two approximations of the area of the region between the graph of the function ${\\it f(x)} = 2{\\it x} + 5$ over the interval $[0, 2]$ using $4$ rectangles.",
        answer: "13, 15",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.2",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //31
        id: 133,
        question: "Find two approximations of the area of the region between the graph of the function ${\\it f(x)} = 2{\\it x}^2 - {\\it x} - 1$ over the interval $[2, 5]$ using $6$ rectangles.",
        answer: "55, 74.5",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.2",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //63
        id: 134,
        question: "Use the Midpoint Rule with ${\\it n} = 4$ to approximate the area of the region between the graph of the function ${\\it f(x)} = {\\it x}^2 +3$ over the interval $[0, 2]$.",
        answer: "69/8",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.2",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //5
        id: 135,
        question: "Use the Trapezoidal Rule with ${\\it n} = 4$ to approximate the integral $ \\int_{3}^{\\>4} \\> \\dfrac {1}{{\\it x}-2} \\>\\it dx$. Round your answer to $4$ decimal places.",
        answer: "0.6970",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.2",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //9
        id: 136,
        question: "Use the Trapezoidal Rule with ${\\it n} = 8$ to approximate the integral $ \\int_{4}^{\\>9} \\> \\sqrt{\\it x} \\>\\it dx$. Round your answer to $4$ decimal places.",
        answer: "12.6640",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.2",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    },
    //--------------------------------------------SECTION 6.3 ----------------------------------
    {
        //17
        id: 137,
        question: "Find the indefinite integral $ \\int {\\it x}^5 +1 \\>\\it dx$.",
        answer: "x^6/6 + x + C",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.3",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //21
        id: 138,
        question: "Find the indefinite integral $ \\int \\sqrt[3]{{\\it x}^2} \\>\\it dx$.",
        answer: "(3/5) x^(5/3) + C",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.3",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //29
        id: 139,
        question: "Find the indefinite integral $ \\int (5\\cos{\\it x} + 4 \\sin{\\it x}) \\>\\it dx$.",
        answer: "5 sin x - 4 cos x + C",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.3",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //31
        id: 140,
        question: "Find the indefinite integral $ \\int (\\csc{\\it x}\\cot{\\it x} -2{\\it x}) \\>\\it dx$.",
        answer: "- csc x - x^2 + C",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.3",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //27
        id: 141,
        question: "Find the indefinite integral $ \\int ({\\it x} +1)(3{\\it x} -2) \\>\\it dx$.",
        answer: "x^3 + (1/2)x^2 - 2x + C",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.3",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    },
    //--------------------------------------------SECTION 6.4 ----------------------------------
    {
        //11
        id: 142,
        question: "Evaluate the definite integral $ \\int _{-1}^{\\>1} {\\it x}^2 - 5 \\>\\it dx$.",
        answer: "-28/3",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.4",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //17
        id: 143,
        question: "Evaluate the definite integral $ \\int _{1}^{\\>4} \\dfrac{{\\it u} - 2}{\\sqrt {\\it u}} \\>\\it du$.",
        answer: "2/3",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.4",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //27
        id: 144,
        question: "Evaluate the definite integral $ \\int _{0}^{\\>4} |{\\it x}^2 - 9| \\>\\it dx$.",
        answer: "64/3",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.4",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //31
        id: 145,
        question: "Evaluate the definite integral $ \\int _{0}^{\\>\\pi/4} \\dfrac{1-\\sin^2\\theta}{\\cos^2\\theta} \\>\\it d\\theta$.",
        answer: "pi/4",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.4",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //41
        id: 146,
        question: "Find the area of the region bounded by ${\\it y} = 5{\\it x}^2 + 2$, ${\\it x} = 0$, ${\\it x} = 2$, and ${\\it y} = 0$.",
        answer: "52/3",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.4",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //43
        id: 147,
        question: "Find the area of the region bounded by ${\\it y} = 1 + \\sqrt[3]{\\it x}$, ${\\it x} = 0$, ${\\it x} = 8$, and ${\\it y} = 0$.",
        answer: "20",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.4",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    },
    //--------------------------------------------SECTION 6.5 ----------------------------------
    {
        //49
        id: 148,
        question: "Find the value(s) of $\\it c$ guaranteed by the Mean Value Theorem for Integrals for the function ${\\it y} = \\dfrac{{\\it x}^2}{4}$ over the interval $[0, 6]$.",
        answer: "c = 2 sqrt 3",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.5",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //53
        id: 149,
        question: "Find the average value of the function ${\\it f(x)} = 4 - {\\it x}^2$ over the interval $[-2, 2]$.",
        answer: "8/3",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.5",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //57
        id: 150,
        question: "Find the average value of the function ${\\it f(x)} = \\sin {\\it x}$ over the interval $[0, \\pi]$.",
        answer: "2/pi",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.5",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //75
        id: 151,
        question: "Use the Second Fundamental Theorem of Calculus to find ${\\it F\\>'(x)}$ for $ {\\it F(x)} = \\int _{-2}^{\\>{\\it x}} ({\\it t}^2 - 2{\\it t}) \\>\\it dt$.",
        answer: "F'(x) = x^2 - 2x",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.5",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //81
        id: 152,
        question: "Find ${\\it F\\>'(x)}$ for $ {\\it F(x)} = \\int _{\\it x}^{\\>{\\it x} + 2} (4{\\it t} + 1) \\>\\it dt$.",
        answer: "F'(x) = 8",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.5",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //85
        id: 153,
        question: "Find ${\\it F\\>'(x)}$ for $ {\\it F(x)} = \\int _{0}^{\\>{\\it x}^3} (\\sin{\\it t}^2) \\>\\it dt$.",
        answer: "F'(x) = 3x^2 sin x^6",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.5",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    },
    //--------------------------------------------SECTION 6.6 ----------------------------------
    {
        //59a
        id: 154,
        question: "A balloon is rising vertically with a velocity of $16$ feet per second. It releases a sandbag at the instant it is $64$ feet above the ground. How many seconds after its release will the bag strike the ground? The acceleration of the object is ${\\it a(t)} = -32. (Round your answer to 3 decimal places.)$",
        answer: "2.562",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.6",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //59b
        id: 155,
        question: "A balloon is rising vertically with a velocity of $16$ feet per second. It releases a sandbag at the instant it is $64$ feet above the ground. At what velocity will the bag hit the ground? The acceleration of the object is ${\\it a(t)} = -32. (Round your answer to 3 decimal places.)$",
        answer: "-65.970",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.6",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //61
        id: 156,
        question: "An object's acceleration is ${\\it a(t)} = -9.8$ meters per second. With what initial velocity must an object be thrown upward from a height of $2$ meters to reach a maximum height of $200$ meters? Round to the nearest tenth.",
        answer: "62.3",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.6",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //65a
        id: 157,
        question: "A particle's position along the $\\it x$-axis is given by ${\\it x(t)} = {\\it t}^3 - 6{\\it t}^2 + 9{\\it t} - 2$. Find the velocity of the particle. Enter your answer as v(t) = ...",
        answer: "v(t) = 6t - 12",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.6",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //65c
        id: 158,
        question: "A particle's position along the $\\it x$-axis is given by ${\\it x(t)} = {\\it t}^3 - 6{\\it t}^2 + 9{\\it t} - 2$. Find the velocity of the particle when the acceleration is $0$.",
        answer: "-3",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.6",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //93a
        id: 159,
        question: "A particle's velocity along the $\\it x$-axis is given by ${\\it v(t)} = 5{\\it t} - 7$. Find the particle's displacement over the interval $0 \\leq {\\it t} \\leq 3$.",
        answer: "3/2",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.6",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //93b
        id: 160,
        question: "A particle's velocity along the $\\it x$-axis is given by ${\\it v(t)} = 5{\\it t} - 7$. Find the total distance the particle travels over the interval $0 \\leq {\\it t} \\leq 3$. Express your answer as a decimal to the nearest tenth.",
        answer: "11.3",
        unit: 6,
        topic: "6.6",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }
];
    
    export default unit6Problems;